Contact

09958127204 (Home) cabagua.joel@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jhon-joel-cabagua-140248169 (LinkedIn) jcdev07.github.io/portfolio/ (Personal)

Top Skills

Git

Responsive Web Design Front-end Development

Jhon Joel Cabagua

Full Stack Developer

Metro Manila

Summary

A former CAD Specialist for more than 3 years. I helped businesses to design and solve problems thru CAD software. I also do coding on the side. That's why after some serious reflection I've started looking into becoming an Full Stack Developer. I know it's a competitive field, but this is the kind of work that's really excites me.

Experience

Zuitt - Coding Bootcamp Philippines

2 months

Postgraduate Student September 2020 - September 2020 (1 month)

Philippines

Capstone 3

- -Created a Fully Functional Websit
- -Features:
- * Booking System
- * Admin Control (CRUD)

Postgraduate Student

August 2020 - August 2020 (1 month)

Philippines

Capstone 2

- -Created an Asset Management Website for a Rental Business
- -Used PHP, Laravel, HTML, CSS

Zuitt - Coding Bootcamp Philippines

Postgraduate Student

June 2020 - June 2020 (1 month)

Philippines

Capstone 1 - Static Website

- Created a Static Website For Burger Restaurant
- Used HTML, CSS, Sass and Bootstrap to Create the Website

GSK Construction and Drafting Services Structural Draftsman January 2019 - January 2020 (1 year 1 month) Philippines

Structural Draftsman

- Creating 3D and 2D Drawings
- Creating Erection & Shop Drawings

Trends Interior Design Pte Ltd 3D Modeler July 2018 - December 2018 (6 months) Singapore, Singapore

3D Modeler

- Creating 3D Models For Commercial Space
- Creating 2D Drawings

ALPA PLUMBING WORKS INC

Autocad Drafter
March 2016 - January 2018 (1 year 11 months)

Autocad Drafter

- Creating AS-Built for Permit and for Construction
- Creating Shop drawings

Education

Zuitt - Coding Bootcamp Philippines
Full Stack Web Developer, Full Stack Web Developer · (2020 - 2020)

Microcadd Technologies Inc Autocad , CAD/CADD Drafting and/or Design Technology/ Technician · (2016 - 2016)